Hey guys and welcome to my 20,000
subscribers COD commentary.
I just moved, and that's why the audio might be a bit shit for the next couple of…
years...
Let's do this.
Do you actually own a Tricorn hat? If so pic please.
No, I want to buy one but they only had
shitty pirate costume hats
So I had no choice...
I would have to desecrate a grave
from the 18th century.
So I did that, but that guy didn't actually have a hat.
I did find seven bottles of champagne though
But what am I going to do with
three-hundred-year-old champagne?
Been watching you since damn early on every video you release is a p nice event for my social circle
We noticed that you seem to be a history/literature buff by you CK2 video and namedrop jokes, so I wonder
did you study history, literature, or is it just a passing interest?
Cheers anyhow and good luck with your patreon!
What are you talking about?
I never make any historic references
Except for that last question, then I made something
but no I don't have any higher education in history nor literature
Nor am I a fan. It's just that...
I'm 1300 years old and sometimes I
forget what's relevant
Why am I immortal? Well when you get to
challenge death
Just remember, he's not very good at
karaoke will you ever make a
Comprehensive in depth examination of why Norway is better than Sweden?
I can't, it's impossible. They are way too
different.
A Friday night in Sweden you might go to a bar right but in Norway they don't have bars. You have to go to
the local tavern and dance with the fair
maidens. In Sweden if you're out of soda
and the store is closed you drink water. In Norway if you're out and the potion
maker has left the village, they grab the fiddle and sing a song about trying new things.
I am a law school graduate, and la la la
dee tee dee ta dee
dido the dye dito am I show up again
November
I hope you can offer us your second term.
Er... good question.
My first term was all about economy and healthcare but now I remember that USA isn't my country
So why do I care?
So for my second term
I've always... I have always wanted to turn
phoenix arizona into a dystopian megacity.
Why Phoenix? Well it's the
largest US city I have never actually heard of
But in the future it would be
known as that dystopian megacity.
Passable accents it's like 4.
I have yet to pull off a passable American accent. Or...
Can I...
Alright!
The game begins with Cloud Strife and his bros doing some terrorist stuff dude
His name is Cloud. Mr. and Mrs. Strife
named after flying water!
He died but let's try
Hey Stephen, is the world better off now
that you're dead? guys it's magic
Guys, it's magic!
First let me tell you the boring fake story
I wanted to do let's plays first, so I recorded one and it was really bad
And then i remembered I don't actually
like let's plays so why should I make them
Two months later I was watching a
completionist episode of a game I already own
And then I thought why watch a review of a game I have completed?
Could I make a review with only jokes? I had just played Life is Strange so I wrote a review on that
Then I uploaded it the next day.
But now let me tell you the REAL story!
I was born in a moon base slum
and every joke I make is something that happens to me in my life.
I have a rule against 100% comment games, Borderland, Conker, Portal etc…
And currently I am avoiding game that would require two parts.
Final fantasy games, Persona games.
Not strategy games…
Not RPGs…
Not FPSs
Actually, I don't have a favorite genre, because I don't like video games.
My favorite video to make was probably Stardew valley, because I got to write my own story
Also, nothing went wrong.
Never got writer's plot, or the game was being an asshole.
Yeah… I guess?
That's a lie! You're a terrible lier!
hur! A cucumber!
But for me…
It was a Tuesday.
Yes.
Yes I did.
I was working on a garbage guide to No man's sky
Turns out… I can't stand the game!
So I'm… I'm very behind on that.
But I might salvage what I have, and create a short video.
I also have the concept for the video « How to beat medium bots ».
But I'm still brainstorming ideas.
In the future I want to do another garbage retrospective
And if we talk about any project… I also want to renovate the bathroom.
Yes…
I mean I just said I want to renovate the bathroom, but I live in a rental.
I can't renovate my bathroom!
Yes.
But not as cool as XXX C country skiing 99
I'm sorry. I can't read Hangul, or speak Japanese.
But I have always wanted to visit Saigon.
Uh… Never really thought about it, maybe I should…
Oh a copyright strike. Well that was fast!
No I like Norway, why would I get rid of them?
If I want to get rid of any country I would go back in time and make it so…
Oh wait, I did. Because fuck you Brittany!
I… I understand the meanings of the words, but I… I can't understand the question.
err… color… correction… surgery?
That makes no sense… I'm sorry, what?
So if I was Swedish I would have to make an Amnesia video?
I'm not some walking stereotype sir.
Dragon age 2
My steam Id is no secret, but I won't add you because its private
my lawyer gave me a tip to stop insider trading
Why ? Its always made me so much money
Its 17 degrees outside
Oh, you mean university degrees. I have all of them
Except history
I said I have a masters, but that's not true.
I do have the 300 university credits
But when I was going to get my degree
My professor told me
I taught him more than he taught me
So I should give him a degree
5 years wasted
My best tip is give up before
you start study math and get a real job
But if you don't want to do that
You can always play mindcraft
I think it's a very strong movie
I would recommend it to anyone
But I do prefer north by northwest by Alfred Hitchcock
But still ice age two is better than batman
V superman
Your probably expecting me to sat halo 4
And thats what Im going to say
I also regret watching batman v superman
What the fuck Sheryll who do you think you are.
Thank you all for the questions
Thank you all for the 100,000 subscribers
And a special thanks to my patron supporters
you know every youtuber say their subscribers are the
best on the site but you guys
Are not but I mean ok
but nothing spectacular
And that is the Kegan experience.